Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Miscellany 5197
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Miscellany
1876-1973
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Illinois Central Gulf Railroad (IC)
5197
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Records of the Illinois Central Gulf Railroad and its predecessor and subsidiary companies, consisting primarily of Rules and Regulations books, Schedules of Wages for various crafts, technical manuals for car builders, and agreements with various unions representing its employees.
5555880
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Elizabeth Parker, May 31, 2017
EAD encoding:
Elizabeth Parker, December 07, 2017
Biographical / Historical
The Illinois Central Railroad [ICRR] was a Class I railroad in the central United States, connecting Chicago with both New Orleans, Louisiana and Mobile, Alabama on its main line.
The ICRR was formed in 1851 when the original investors succeeded in obtaining a large land grant from the federal government for the purpose of building a railroad under provisions granted by the Douglas Land Grant Bill. The grant was particularly generous, and the railroad expanded rapidly. The expansion was so rapid that the Illinois Central was one of the world's largest railroads by the time of the Civil War, branching out from Chicago westward to Sioux City, Iowa and southward to Cairo, Illinois. During the latter part of the nineteenth century and first two decades of the twentieth, the ICRR continued to add mileage to its holdings. This was especially the case in the south where the company succeeded in connecting Cairo with New Orleans. By the onset of the Great Depression, the Illinois Central controlled almost 5000 miles of track and was one of America's largest railroads.
As the twentieth century progressed, the ICRR, like the railroad industry in general, came under increasing pressure from new forms of transportation, especially the automobile. As a result, it began to experience shrinking profit margins and depressed markets for its services. The ICRR responded by implementing technologically advanced operating equipment, such as the diesel engine, cutting back on certain service, such as passenger service, and eliminating what it viewed as antiquated work practices among its employees.
This last aspect of the ICRR's response to its new operating environment produced acute struggles between the railroad unions and the railroad itself, culminating in the Presidential Emergency Board mandated elimination through attrition of virtually all firemen's positions in 1963. The ICRR's final response to its depressed situation was to merge with the Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio railroad in 1972 to form the Illinois Central Gulf Railroad. In 1998, the ICRR was purchased by the Canadian National Railway and integrated into its operations.
Scope and Contents
Inclusive date range: 1876-1973
Bulk dates: 1898-1968
This collection is comprised of records from the Illinois Central Railroad [ICRR]. The bulk of the materials are rule books, schedules of wages, car-builder manuals, rules and regulations, codes of rules for the interchange of traffic, agreements with predecessor and subsidiary railroads, agreements with railroad unions, and telegraph codes used by the company. There are rule and regulation books and wage schedules for the various classes and crafts of railroad employees; they are also divided geographically. For example, a conductor on the Chicago passenger line had a different set of rules and wage schedule from a yardman in New Orleans. Some books also predate ICRR's absorption of other subsidiary roads and as such are specific to the employees of those smaller lines. Also found are rules and regulations from the United States Railroad Administration during its control of American railroads during World War I.
Also found in this collection is an internal document outlining the ICRR's plans for its centennial celebrations in 1951. The pamphlet describes the various celebrations, commemorative items, such as plaques, medals, monuments, and books, and advertising strategies to capitalize on the occasion. The pamphlet contains photographs of many of these items, some of which may be found in collection 5197 MB.
Of particular interest are the pamphlets for the Gold Pass Luncheons. These annual celebrations feted railroad employees who had been with the company for fifty years. Each program contains the name of each veteran employee along with a photograph and a brief biography of the employee.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5197 MB: Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Memorabilia 5295: Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Company Selected Personnel Files 5481 AV: Railroad Industrial Relations Project Oral History Interviews Audiorecordings 5943: Dan A. Ballard Collection of Railroad Memorabilia & Wage Information
Railroads -- Illinois -- History; Railroad cars -- Design and construction; Railroads -- Buildings and structures -- Illinois; Railroads -- Employees; Wages -- Railroads -- United States; Industrial relations -- United States; Collective bargaining -- Railroads -- United States; Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Company; Association of American Railroads; United States Railroad Administration; Master Car Builders' Association; Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad Company; Alabama and Vicksburg Railway; Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad; Paducah and Illinois Railroad Company; Missouri Pacific Railroad Company; Mississippi Central Railroad Company; Gulf and Ship Island Railroad Company
5555880
- Association of American Railroads Code of Rules, 1930-1938 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Code Of Rules, 1938; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Association of American Railroads, Code of Rules: Governing the Condition of, And Repairs to, Freight and Passenger Cars for the Interchange of Traffic
    Format: Pamphlet.
  - Item 2: Code of Rules, 1937; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Code of Rules, 1936; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Code of Rules, 1932; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Code of Rules, 1930; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Code of Rules, 1931; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Association of American Railroads Code of Rules, 1939-1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Code of Rules, 1942; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Code of Rules, 1939; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Code of Rules, 1944; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Association of American Railroads-Interchange Rules, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Code of Rules, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Code of Rules, 1968; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Code of Rules, 1969; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Code of Rules, 1967; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Association of American Railroads-Field Manual, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Field Manual, 1970; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Field Manual of the A.A.R. Interchange Rules
  - Item 2: Field Manual, 1971; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Illinois Railroad 1951 Centennial (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Plans for the Centennial celebrations for the ICRR
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Railroad, 1951; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Illinois Central Railroad, 1951 Centennial
- Association of American Railroads-Code of Rules, 1919-1943 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Code of Rules, 1919; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Code of Rules, 1929; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Code of Rules, 1943; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Code of Rules, 1928; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Association of American Railroads-Code of Rules, 1920-1926 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Code of Rules, 1920; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Code of Rules, 1925; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Code of Rules, 1923; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Code of Rules, 1921; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Code of Rules, 1922; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Code of Rules, 1926; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Association of American Railroads-Code of Rules, 1927-1941 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Code of Rules, 1935; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Code of Rules, 1940; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Code of Rules, 1933; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Code of Rules, 1941; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Code of Rules, 1927; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Code of Rules, 1934; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Master Car Builders Association-Code of Rules, 1896-1910 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  1896, 1897, 1898, 1899, 1900, 1901, 1902, 1903, 1905, 1907, 1909, 1910
  - Item 1: Code of Rules, 1905; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Master Car Builders' Association, Code of Rules: Governing the Condition of, And Repairs to, Freight Cars for the Interchange of Traffic
  - Item 2: Code of Rules, 1900; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Code of Rules, 1907; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Code of Rules, 1896; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Code of Rules, 1901; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Code of Rules, 1909; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Code of Rules, 1897; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Code of Rules, 1902; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Code of Rules, 1910; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Code of Rules, 1903; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Code of Rules, 1898; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Code of Rules, 1899; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Master Car Builders Association-Code of Rules, 1894-1914 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Code of Rules, 1894; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Code of Rules, 1895; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Code of Rules, 1906; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Code of Rules, 1904; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Code of Rules, 1908; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Code of Rules, 1911; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Code of Rules, 1912; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Code of Rules, 1913; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Code of Rules, 1914; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Association of American Railroads-Interchange Rules, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  1965
  - Item 1: Code of Rules, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Code of Rules: Supplement 1, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Code of Rules: Supplement 2, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Association of American Railroads-Code of Rules, 1949-1955 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Code of Rules, 1952; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Code of Rules, 1953; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Code of Rules, 1954; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Code of Rules, 1955; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Code of Rules, 1949; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Code of Rules, 1950; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Association of American Railroads-Code of Rules, 1948-1960 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Code of Rules, 1951; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Code of Rules, 1948; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Code of Rules, 1958; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Code of Rules, 1947; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Code of Rules, 1959; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Code of Rules, 1960; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Association of American Railroads-Code of Rules, 1945-1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  1945,1946, 1956, 1957, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1964
  - Item 1: Code of Rules, 1945; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Code of Rules, 1946; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Code of Rules, 1956; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Code of Rules, 1961; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Code of Rules, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Code of Rules, 1957; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Code of Rules, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Code of Rules, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Illinois Central System-Rules, Schedules, and Instruction booklets for employees, 1912-1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Rules and Instructions, 1954; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad, Rules and Instructions for Train Handling and Operation of Air Brakes on Locomotives and Cars
  - Item 2: Examination Questions, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Examination Questions for Locomotive Enginemen
  - Item 3: Rules and Instructions, 1912; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Rules and Instructions Governing Free Travel and Passes
  - Item 4: Schedule of Rules and Working Conditions, 1934; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Rules and Working Conditions Governing the Several Classes of Employees in the Maintenance of Way and Structures Department
  - Item 5: Schedule of Rules and Working Conditions, 1922; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Rules and Working Conditions for Employees Represented by the Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees
  - Item 6: Schedule of Rules, 1935; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Rules Governing the Working Conditions of Stationary Engineers, Firemen, and Oilers, Roundhouse and Shop Laborers
  - Item 7: Rules and Specifications, 1947; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Rules and Specifications Governing the Unfirming of Employees
  - Item 8: Schedule of Rules and Working Conditions, 1922; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Rules and Working Conditions for Employees Represented by the Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employes
- Illinois Central Railroad-Schedule of Wages for various crafts in multiple locations, 1876-1941 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Schedule of Wages for Trainmen, 1911; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages for Trainmen in Passenger and Freight Service
  - Item 2: Schedule of Wages for Trainmen, 1911; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Schedule of Wages and Rules for Trainmen, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages and Rules for Trainmen in Passenger and Freight Service
  - Item 4: Schedule of Wages and Rules for Conductors, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages and Rules for Conductors in Suburban Passenger Service, Chicago
  - Item 5: Schedule of Wages and Rules for Conductors, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Schedule of Wages and Rules for Trainmen, 1920; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Firemen, 1921; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Firemen
  - Item 8: Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Firemen, 1927; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Firemen, 1925; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Firemen, 1921; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Schedule of Wages and Rules for Trainmen, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages and Rules for Trainmen in Suburban Service, Chicago
  - Item 12: Schedule of Wages for Trainmen, 1911; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages for Trainmen in Suburban Passenger Service at Chicago
  - Item 13: Schedule of Wages and Rules for Trainmen, 1914; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages and Rules for Trainmen in Suburban Passenger Service, Chicago
  - Item 14: Schedule of Wages and Rules for Trainmen, 1920; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Schedule of Locomotive Engineers, 1941; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Locomotive Engineers
  - Item 16: Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Engineers, 1911; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Schedule of Locomotive Engineers, 1913; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Schedule of Locomotive Engineers, 1915; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Schedule of Locomotive Engineers, 1920; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Schedule of Wages for Locomotive Firemen, 1876; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Engineers and Firemen (photo copy)
  - Item 21: Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Engineers and Firemen, 1885; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Engineers and Firemen, 1890; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: Schedule of Wages and Rules Governing Yardmen and Switchtenders, 1920; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages and Rules Governing Yardmen and Switchtenders
  - Item 24: Schedule of Wages and Rules Governing Yardmen and Switchtenders, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Schedule of Wages for Yardmen, 1913; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages for Yardmen at Chicago, IL.
  - Item 26: Schedule of Wages for Switchmen, 1906; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages for Switchmen
  - Item 27: Schedule of Wages for Switchmen, 1906; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central railroad Co., Schedule of Wages for Switchmen at Chicago, IL.
  - Item 28: Schedule of Wages for Switchmen, 1910; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages for Switchmen at Chicago, IL
  - Item 29: Schedules of Wages and Rules, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages and Rules for Conductors
  - Item 30: Schedules of Wages and Rules, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 31: Schedule of Wages for Switchmen, 1906; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages for Switchmen at New Orleans, LA.
  - Item 32: Schedule of Wages for Switchmen, 1910; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 33: Schedule of Wages for Switchmen, 1914; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages and Rules Governing Switching Service at New Orleans
  - Item 34: Schedule of Wages for Switching Service, 1906; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages for Switching Service at Points Named
  - Item 35: Schedule of Wages for Switching Service, 1910; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 36: Schedule of Wages for Switching Service, 1911; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages for Switching Service, Points Named
  - Item 37: Schedule of Wages, 1914; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Illinois Central Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages and Rules Governing Switching Service at Points Named
- Illinois Central System-Cipher Code Books, 1927-1929 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Standard Cipher Code, 1927; White Cipher Code, 1929
  - Item 1: White Cipher Code Book, 1914; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Illinois Central System Operating Department, White Cipher Code (for the use of Director of Personnel, in Chicago)
  - Item 2: Standard Cipher Code Book, 1910; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Illinois Central System Operating Department, Standard Cipher Code (for the use of R.J. McLean, in Memphis)
- Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad Company-Rules Book and Schedule of Wages Book, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  August, 1927
  - Item 1: Rules and Regulations, 1927; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 4)
    The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad Co., Rules and Regulations concerning Locomotive Firemen, Hostlers, and Helpers
  - Item 2: Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Firemen, 1927; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 4)
    The Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad Co., Schedule of Wages of Locomotive Firemen
- Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad-Rates of Pay and Rules for various crafts, 1894-1937 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Rates of Pay, 1912; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad- Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Conductors, Trainmen, and Yardmen
  - Item 2: Rates of Pay, 1912; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Rates of Pay, 1901; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad- Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Locomotive Engineers
  - Item 4: Rates of Pay, 1902; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad- Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Trainmen
  - Item 5: Rates of Pay, 1903; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Rates of Pay, 1906; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Rates of Pay, 1906; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Rates of Pay, 1906; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Rates of Pay, 1909; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Rates of Pay, 1909; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Rates of Pay, 1909; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Rates of Pay, 1910; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad- Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Conductors, White Trainmen, and White Yardmen
  - Item 13: Rates of Pay, 1910; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Rates of Pay, 1912; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad- Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Trainmen and Yardmen
  - Item 15: Rates of Pay, 1911; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Rates of Pay, 1917; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Rates of Pay, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad- Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Locomotive Firemen, Hostlers and Helpers
  - Item 18: Rates of Pay, 1925; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad- Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Conductors and Trainmen
  - Item 19: Rates of Pay, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: Rates of Pay, 1917; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad- Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Conductors, Trainmen and Yardmen
  - Item 21: Rules and Regulations, 1925; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad- Rules and Regulations concerning Locomotive Firemen, Hostlers and Helpers
  - Item 22: Rules and Regulations, 1925; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad- Rules and Regulations concerning Switchmen
  - Item 23: Rates of Pay, 1898; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad- Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Engineers
  - Item 24: Rates of Pay, 1898; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 25: Rates of Pay, 1898; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad and Alabama and Vicksburg Railway- Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Engineers
- Alabama and Vicksburg Railway-Rates of Pay and Rules for various crafts, 1898-1946 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Rates of Pay, 1898; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Alabama and Vicksburg Railway-Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Trainmen
  - Item 2: Rates of Pay, 1912; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Alabama and Vicksburg Railway-Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Conductors, Trainmen and Yardmen
  - Item 3: rates of Pay, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
    The Alabama and Vicksburg Railway-Rates of Pay and other Regulations concerning Locomotive Engineers
  - Item 4: Rates of Pay, 1924; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)